Guide to the Louis H. Roddis Papers, 1823-1990 RL.01102
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Contracts Series, 1958-1982 and undated
  - Institute of Gas Technology Invoices, 1978-1982 (Box 94)
  - Don Howard Correspondence, 1976 Oct. 22 (Box 94)
  - NRC- Puerto Rico, 1979-1980 (Box 94)
  - APL Consulting, 1977-1979 (Box 94)
  - Washington Public Power Supply Systems Contracts, 1980-1982 (Box 94)
  - Egler and Reinstadtler, 1981 (Box 94)
  - Sierra Pacific Research Corporation, 1976-1979 (Box 94)
  - EBASCO Services, Inc., 1976 July 28 (Box 94)
  - Management Analysis Company Contract, 1976 (Box 94)
  - Standards of Conduct for the White House Staff, 1974 (Box 94)
- Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI) 1976-1986
  Consists of briefings, annual reports, and programs concerning acid rain, electric power, public policy aspects of high-capacity electric power transmission, research and development programs concerning electricity supply and demand, efficient and safe facilities, fuel supply, and environmental protection.
  - Briefing Paper on Acid Rain, 1983 June 1 (Box 94)
  - Presentation, 1986 May 15 (Box 94)
  - 1982-1986 Overview of Strategy and Executive Summary, 1982 Apr. (Box 94)
  - Blue Ribbon Overview and Strategy Review Committee Meeting, 1979 Nov. 15-16 (Box 94)
  - 1981-1985 Overview and Strategy: Executive Summary, 1980 Oct. (Box 94)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 94)
  - Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 94)
  - Generating Capacity in U.S. Electric Utilities: An Update, 1984 Dec. (Box 94)
  - Electric Power Research Institute Journal Cumulative Index to Feature Articles, 1976-1985 (Box 94)
  - Aspen Center for Physics, 1978 (Box 94)
  - Aspen Program and Letters, 1979 (Box 94)
  - Physics-Astrophysics Program at the Aspen Center for Physics, 1979 June 4-Aug. 31 (Box 94)
  - Aspen, 1979 (Box 94)
  - Aspen Speakers, 1979 (Box 94)
  - Aspen- Harvard, 1979 June 12 (Box 94)
  - Aspen Conference, 1979 May 14-16 (Box 94)
- John J. McMullen Associates Series, 1976-1980 and undated
  Consists of articles, notes, memoranda, brochures, booklets, meeting minutes, correspondence, and reports. Roddis worked with John J. McMullen Associates, Inc. which was a consulting firm that worked with naval architecture and marine engineering.
  - OTEC Mooring and Transmission Manuscript, 1977 Nov. 16 (Box 94)
  - OTEC, 1977 (Box 94)
  - OTEC, 1978 July 10 (Box 94)
  - Coal, 1979 Dec. 2 (Box 94)
  - Coal, Oil, and Gas, 1980 (Box 94)
  - Foreign Military Sales (FMS) Canada, 1976 (Box 94)
  - FMS, 1976 (Box 94)
  - Experience and Capabilities in Energy Transportation, undated (Box 94)
  - Marine Facilities Development, 1977 Sept. (Box 94)
  - Correspondence, 1977 Sept. 15 (Box 94)
  - Brochures, undated (Box 94)
  - Naval Ships and Systems, 1977 Jan. (Box 94)
  - Detail Design and Engineering, undated (Box 94)
  - Proposal for an Interim LNG Import Facility, 1977 Aug. (Box 94)
- Committees and Panels Series, 1966-1990
  Consists of correspondence, notes, memoranda, brochures, newletters, agenda, meeting minutes, bulletin, and reports from selected committees and panels on which Roddis served.
  - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC)-Panel on Safeguarding Special Nuclear Material Oraganization, 1966 (Box 94)
  - AEC-Advisory Committee on Nuclear Materials Safeguards, 1966-1969 (Box 94)
  - Governor's Science Advisory Committee, 1967 (Box 94)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) Committee on Radioactive Waste Management, 1968-1969 (Box 94)
  - Shea and Gould, 1988 Feb. 4 (Box 95)
  - Conference Internationale de Grands Reseaux Electrique a Haute Tension/ International Conference on Large High Voltage Electrical Systems (C.I.G.R.E.): (Box 95)
  - 1984 Directory of U.S. National Committee, 1984 Dec. 31 (Box 95)
  - Conference Subjects and U.S. National Committee Directory, 1982 (Box 95)
  - U.S. National Committee Memoranda, 1980-1989 (Box 95)
  - General Assembly Correspondence, 1980-1990 (Box 95)
  - Booklets, Bulletins, and Correspondence, 1980-1990 (Box 95)
  - 1990 Directory of U.S. National Committee, 1990 July 31 (Box 95)
  - By-laws, 1980-1987 (Box 95)
  - Energy Systems and Policy Editorial Board, 1973-1989 (Box 95)
- Berlin Energy Congress, 1974-1978 and undated
  Consists of pamphlets, brochures, reports, photographs, diagrams, slides, transparencies, correspondence, invitations, clippings, and notes from the Berlin Energy Congress. This is an annual congress held in Berlin to discuss possibilities for energy uses, modification of current methods, and ideas for more efficient energy uses. Roddis was a speaker at the congress on the rational use of energy.
  - Speech Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 95)
  - Correspondence with New York Companies, 1975-1976 (Box 95)
  - AMK Berlin Materials on Rational Use of Energy Conurbations (Box 95)
  - 1976 Sept. (Box 95)
  - Siemens' Dynamowerk Berlin, undated (Box 95)
  - Sonnenschein Pamphlets, undated (Box 95)
  - Kernkraftewerke Pamphlets, 1974 (Box 95)
  - Berlin Tourism Information, 1976 (Box 95)
  - Braunkohlenbergbau und Landschaftsgestaltung im Rheinischen River, 1975 Apr. (Box 95)
  - Kongress--Rationelle Energienutzung in Ballungsgebieten, 1976 July (Box 95)
  - Background Information on New York City's Infrastructure, 1976 Sept. (Box 95)
- Testimonies and Depositions Series, 1970-1988 and undated
  Consists of testimonies and despositions given by Roddis, often as an expert witness, to support companies of which he had been a Board member or to which he had been a consulting engineer.
  - Securities Exchange Commission Testimony of Louis H. Roddis, Jr. in the AEP-Columbus and Southern Case, Vol. 1. 1970-1971 (Box 95)
  - PG&E Testimony, 1987 July (Box 95)
  - Oral Deposition of Louis H. Roddis, Jr. in City of Austin vs. Houston Lighting and Power, 1987 June 25 (Box 96)
  - Oral Deposition of Louis H. Roddis, Jr. in City of Austin vs. Houston Lighting and Power, 1987 June 26 (Box 96)
  - Louis H. Roddis, Jr. Rebuttal Testimony in Long Island Lighting Company Shoreham Facility Case, undated (Box 96)
  - Supporting Documents in AEP-Columbus and Southern Case, Vol. 2, 1970-1971 (Box 96)
  - Deposition of Louis H. Roddis, Jr. in Commonwealth Edison Company Proposed General Increase in Electric Rates, 1988 Aug. 28 (Box 96)
- Liquified Natural Gas Imports LNG, 1977-1978 and undated
  Consists of statements given at the Department of Energy's Public Hearing on Federal Government Policy for LNG. Series covers such issues as the development of a national policy on liquified natural gas imports, shipment of LNG imports, pricing, safety, and excavation of LNG.
  - Oral Testimony of Dr. Paul W. Tucker at the Hearing on Federal Government Policy for LNG Imports, 1977 Dec. 29 (Box 96)
  - Department of Energy Hearings and Proceedings, undated (Box 96)
  - Statement of Fred. H. Bixby Ranch Company on LNG Imports before the Department of Energy, 1978 Jan. 3 (Box 96)
  - Statement OF Robert R. Nathan before the Federal Government Interagency Task Force on LNG Imports, 1978 Jan. 4 (Box 96)
  - Testimony of Nevil M.E. Proesat the Hearing of the Federal Interagency Task Force on LNG Imports, 1978 Jan. 5 (Box 96)
  - Department of Energy Public Hearing on Federal Government Policy for Liquified Natural Gas Schedule of Presentations, 1978 Jan. 5 (Box 96)
  - Testimony of John M. Murphy at the Hearings on Federal Government Policy on LNG Imports, 1978 Jan. 4 (Box 96)
- Gas Research Series, 1977-1986 and undated
  Contains reports, brochures, pamphlets, correspondence, proposals, speeches, news releases, a newsletter, and booklets. The series is made up of two main agencies: Gas Research Institute (GRI) and Institute of Gas Technology (IGT), both of which dedicate their efforts to discovering innovations in efficiency and safety with natural gas. The focus of this series is the GRI and IGT research of efficient uses of gas in order to repeal the Power Plant and Industrial Fuel Act which required utilities to go back to predominantly using coal so as not to deplete the supply of gas and petroleum.
  - Gas Research Institute Annual Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 96)
  - GRI 's 10th Annual Meeting of Members, 1986 Apr. 10 (Box 96)
  - GRI's Current Outlook for Natural Gas Supply, 1985 June (Box 96)
  - The Nonnuclear Alvin Weinberg, 1985 Mar. 15 (Box 96)
  - GRI Correspondence, 1985 (Box 96)
  - Oil and Gas Journal Articles, 1985 Oct. 28 (Box 96)
  - U.S. Energy Supply and Demand, 1985 (Box 96)
  - Advanced Fuel Cell Concepts--Systems Evaluation, 1979 Nov. 19 (Box 96)
  - GRI's Project 30514: On-Site Molten Carbonate Fuel Cells, 1979 (Box 96)
  - GRI's 1981-1985 Five Year Research and Development Plan and 1981 Research and Development Program, 1980 Mar. 27 (Box 96)
  - Institute of Gas Technology Visit, 1979 July 25 (Box 96)
  - IGT--Small Utility, 1980 Jan. 16 (Box 96)
  - IGT's Advance Technology for Clean Energy Merging Molten Carbonate Fuel Cells and Coal Gasification, undated (Box 96)
  - IGT Correspondence, 1978 and 1980 (Box 96)
  - IGT's Integrated Molten Carbonate Fuel Cell/Coal Gasifier Power (Box 96)
  - System 1978 Mar. 31 (Box 96)
  - IGT Annual Report, 1977 (Box 96)
  - IGT Miscellaneous, 1977-1979 (Box 96)
  - IGT's Status of Molten Carbonate Fuel Cell Technology, 1981 Mar. 9-11 (Box 96)
  - IGT's Fuel Cells for Future Power Booklet, undated (Box 96)
  - Final Report to Project 65043 Application of Cogeneration to Michigan Industry 1980 Dec. 5 (Box 96)
  - IGT Nuclear Power in Washington Notes, 1980 Aug. 8 (Box 96)
  - IGT Project S-128 Symposium, 1980 June 6, 1980 June 6 (Box 96)
  - Mechanical Technology Incorporated Materials, 1980 (Box 96)
  - Electricity Generation from Renewable Sources Using Fuel Cells, 1979 (Box 96)
- Ashrae Handbook Series, 1982-1989
  Series contains mechanical and engineering reference books.
  - Refrigeration-Systems and Applications, 1986 (volume) (Box 97)
  - Heating, Ventilating, and Air Conditioning (HVAC) Systems and Applications, 1987 (volume) (Box 97)
  - Equipment, 1988 (volume) (Box 97)
  - Fundamentals, 1989 (volume) (Box 97)
  - Ashrae Product Specification File, 1982 (volume) (Box 97)
- Renewable Energy Institute Series, 1977-1987
  Consists of correspondence, reports, REI president's U.S. Senate testimony, board meetings' packets which contained the agenda, programming summary, financial report, directory of the board members and meeting minutes, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission testimony, and memoranda. Issues discussed range from small power production and cogeneration to renewable energy technologies. The Renewable Energy Institute (REI) is an organization based in Washington, D.C. that is concerned with the United States' alternative energy sources that are renewable (such as solar power and wind power).
  - Minutes of Board Meeting, 1986, Mar. 13 (Box 97)
  - Material from Mar. 13, 1986 Board of Directors' Meeting, 1985-1986 (Box 97)
  - Board of Directors Material, 1986-1987 (Box 97)
  - Follow-up to Apr. 7 Board Meeting by Frank M. Potter, 1987, Apr. 16 (Box 97)
  - Nomination letter for Frank Potter, 1986, Aug. 5 (Box 97)
  - Material from 1985, Oct. 22 Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 97)
  - Correspondence on Board of Directors' Meeting, 1985-1986 (Box 97)
  - Renewable Energy Institute (REI), 1985 (Box 97)
  - Board of Directors' and Task Force Correspondence, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Board of Directors' Meeting, 1983, Nov. 17 (Box 97)
  - Burns and Roe: Proposal, 1986 (Box 97)
  - REI: Correspondence ( 1987-1988) (Box 97)
  - Information on the Research Group International, 1977 (Box 97)
  - REI: Rhode Island: PUC, 1978 (Box 97)
  - Presidential Achievement Awards, undated (Box 97)
  - Utility Decision-Making Draft, 1986 (Box 97)
  - Exhibits from April 15 Utility Task Force Meeting, 1987 (Box 97)
  - Materials on Utility Industry Polity Task Force Meeting on July 13-15, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Renewable Energy Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 97)
  - RPA McWhinny, 1982 (Box 97)
  - Republician National Committee Certificate, 1983 (Box 97)
  - Written Testimony on Cogeneration and Samll Power Production, 1987 (Box 97)
  - Trends in State Utility Regulation Affecting Renewable Energy, 1987, Mar. (Box 97)
  - Summary of Financial Status, 1987, Aprl 7 (Box 97)
  - U.S. Testimony by Frank M. Potter, 1987, Mar. 26Annual Renewable Energy Technology Review, 1986 (Box 97)
- Three Mile Island Accident, 1980-1988 (Continued)
  See also boxes 40-42.
  - 27-58 TMI-2 Recovery Project: Volume 3 Part 2, 3 folders (Box 98)
  - 27-59 TMI-2 Recovery Project: Volume 3 Part 1, 4 folders (Box 98)
  - 27-60 TMI-2 Recovery Project: Volume 3 Part 3, 3 folders (Box 98)
  - 27-61 TMI-2 Recovery Project: Volume 3 Part 4, 4 folders (Box 98)
  - 27-66 TMI-2 Recovery Project: Volume 3 Part 9, 4 folders (Box 98)
  - 27-67 TMI-2 Recovery Project: Technical Data Book, Vol. 1 (Box 98)
  - 27-68 TMI-2 Recovery Project: Technical Data Book, Vol. 2, 3 folders (Box 99)
  - 27-69 TMI-2 Recovery Project: Technical Plan for Reactor Building, 3 folders (Box 99)
  - 27-71 TMI-2: Appendix "A:, 3 folders (Box 99)
  - 27-72 TMI-2: Nuclear Generating Technical Specification, Vol. 12, 5 folders (Box 99)
  - 27-73 TMI-2: Nuclear Generating Set of Reduced Scale Plans, 4 folders (Box 99)
  - 27-74 TMI 1: Technical Specifications: Metropolitan Edison Co., 2 folders (Box 99)
  - TMI Unit 1 Nuclear Generating Station Plan Systems, 1983, Apr. 28 (Box 100)
  - TMI-2 Ra and Con (Box 100)
  - Saxton, 1988, Nov. 18 (Box 100)
  - GPU Nuclear Statements Before U.S. House of Representatives Subcommittee on Energy and the Environment, 1983, Apr. 26 (Box 100)
  - Three Mile Island Unit 2: A Strategy for Recovery Program completion and Post-Recovery Configuration:
    - Vol. 1: Executive summary, 1986, July (Box 100)
    - Vol. 2: A Technical Basis, 1986, July (Box 100)
    - Vol. 3: Appendices, 1986, July (Box 100)
  - TMI and the Environment: A Report on the TMI Effluent and Environmental Monitoring Program (Box 100)
  - EPRI Memorandum: TMI-2 Technical History Project Announcement, 1987, Jan. 26 (Box 100)
  - Report of the TMI-1 Operator Accelerated Retraining Program Review Committee, 1980, June 1 (Box 100)
  - General Public Utilities Nuclear: TMI Unit 1 Reactor Vessel Internals, 1984, Dec. 6 (Box 100)
  - GPU's Three Mile Island Unit 2 Plannng Study for Containment Entry and Decontamination, 1979, July 2 (Box 100)
  - Met-Ed/GPU Summary Technical Plan for TMI-2 Decontamination and Defueling, 1979, Dec. 12 (Box 100)
  - Three Mile Island Unit 2 Recovery Quarterly Progress Report:
    - Period Ending June 30, 1980, 1980, July 15 (Box 100)
    - Period Ending Sept. 30, 1980, 1980, Oct. 15 (Box 100)
  - TMI-2 Initial Planning Study Supplement No. 1, 1980, Feb. 11 (Box 100)
  - TMI-2 Planning Study for Phase II: Reactor Internals Disassembly, Fuel Removal, and System Cleanup: Bechtel Power Corporation, 1980, May 28 (Box 100)
- Miscellaneous
  Consists of articles, clippings, newsletters, correspondence, training manuals, reports, memorandums, annual reports, photographs, and drafts. Topics include ocean thermal energy conversion (OTEC), International Thormonuclear Experimental Reactor (ITER), General Public Utilites, nuclear power reports, various power plants and state power companies, and the U.S.S. Nautilus.
  - Letters to the Editors of the Washington Post and The New York Times, 1981, Sept. 4 (Box 101)
  - Correspondence and article, 1980, Jan. (Box 101)
  - New York Times article and correspondence, 1981, Dec. 15 (Box 101)
  - Connecticut Gas & Electricity Wall Street Journal clipping, 1984, Sept. 26 (Box 101)
  - Wall Street Journal clipping, 1985, Aug. 15 (Box 101)
  - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 101)
  - Scientific American article, 1986, Mar. (Box 101)
  - Nuclear News articles, 1985, July-1986, Nov., 4 folders (Box 101)
  - INFO (Report on public understanding of nuclear energy), 1986, May (Box 101)
  - Electrical World articles, 1963-1987, Oct., 6 folders (Box 101)
  - IEEE Spectrum, 1985, Apr. (Box 101)
  - IEEE Spectrum article:
    - Whatever Happened to National Electric Grid? 1985, June (Box 101)
    - Article, 1986, Feb. (Box 101)
  - EEE Power Engineering Review article, 1986, Mar. (Box 101)
  - Nuclear News articles, 1986, Apr. (Box 101)
  - MIT E-Lab Newsletter, 1984, Oct.-Dec. (Box 101)
  - Electrical Week, 1982, Dec. 13 (Box 101)
  - Public Utilities: Fortnightly, 1981-1988, 11 folders (Box 101)
  - Department of Energy News, 1981, Oct. 28 (Box 101)
  - Fusion Power Associates:
    - Board of Directors: Policy statements, 1985-1986, undated, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 101)
    - Executive Newsletter, 1985-1986; 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - News from, 1985-1986 (Box 101)
    - What's News in Fusion, 1984-1986; 1987, Apr.-Sept.; 1987-1990, 3 folders (Box 101)
    - Newsletters, 1990, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Paraphernalia, 1988-1989 (Box 101)
  - Fusion Canada: News Bulletins, 1988, May, Aug.; 1989-1990, 3 folders (Box 101)
  - U.S. Council for Energy Awareness: Info newsletters, 1987-1991, 2 folders (Box 101)
  - EPRI News, 1973, Aug. (Box 101)
  - Inside N.R.C.
    - U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission newsletters, 1986-1990, 6 folders (Box 101)
    - Article, 1985, June 24 (Box 101)
    - An Exclusive Report in the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1989, Sept. 25 (Box 101)
  - Gas-Cooled Reactor Associates newsletters, 1990 (Box 101)
  - The Soviet-East European Program of the National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council Newsletter, 1989, spring ed. (Box 101)
  - Articles on Nuclear Energy, 1981-1983 (Box 101)
  - Feeds News, 1985, May (Box 101)
  - Independent Power Report article, 1989, Mar. (Box 101)
  - Business Week's Rankings of the Utility Industry, 1989, Apr. (Box 101)
  - Offshore Power Systems: Materials, 1972-1977, 2 folders (Box 102)
  - Oceans '78--The Ocean Challenge, 1978, Sept. 6-8 (Box 102)
  - OTEC (Ocean Termal Energy Conversion):
    - John Hopkins Applied Physics Lab, 1978-1979, undated, 4 folders
      - Contract Files, 1977-1978, 4 folders (Box 102)
      - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 102)
      - Review of Solar Energy, 1978, Aug. 11 (Box 102)
      - Memorandum, 1978, Oct. 25 (Box 102)
      - Gulf States Utilities, 1979 (Box 102)
    - Consolidated Edison Company: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 102)
    - Perspectives on Implementing OTEC Power: Florida Power & Light, 1978, June 9 (Box 102)
    - 10/20 Mile Pilot Plant Cost Estimates, 1978, Sept. 18
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979, Feb. 1 (Box 102)
      - Offshore Technology Conference: Missions and Commercial (Box 102)
      - Opportunities, 1978 (Box 102)
      - Ammonia Fuel Cell materials, undated (Box 102)
      - Maps, undated (Box 102)
  - DTC: Technology for the Dredging World, undated (Box 102)
  - Office of Technology Assessment:
    - n. d. (Box 102)
    - OTEC Report, undated (Box 102)
  - International Thermonuclear Experimental Reactor:
    - Newsletter, 1989, Feb., undated, 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Activities Status Report, 1989, Dec. (Box 102)
  - ITER Activities Status Report, 1989, Dec. (Box 102)
  - Initial Report of the ITER Council's Ways and Means Working Party, 1990 (Box 102)
  - Issues in Science and Technology: Article, 1990, Feb. 20 (Box 102)
  - Correspondence, 1990, Mar. 1 (Box 102)
  - GPU:
    - Systems Operations Training Program, 1979, Oct. 23 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence, 1980, Apr. 11 (Box 102)
    - Nuclear materials, 1981-1984 (Box 102)
  - General Public Utilities Corporation Respond to NRC Commission's Memo, 1983, Aug. 4 (Box 102)
  - GPU Nuclear Corporation Supervisor's Manual, 1985, Feb. 15 (Box 102)
  - Oyster Creek Nuclear Power Generating Plant materials, 1963-1968 (Box 102)
  - Oyster Creek Nuclear Generating Station Important Dates, Facts, and Statistics, 1982, Apr. 1 (Box 102)
  - TMI-2 Occupational Radiation Exposure Report, 1979-1987, Apr. (Box 102)
  - GPU Nuclear: Memorandum, 1989, Jan. 12-Oct. 13, 2 folders (Box 102)
  - GPU Nuclear's Today: Vol. 10, No. 1, 1989, Spring edition (Box 102)
  - GPU Penelac Annual Reports, 1958-1969 (Box 102)
  - Pictures, 1980, Jan. 22 (Box 102)
  - GPU's Report of the Ad-Hoc Advisory Committees on Personal Selection and Training Man-Machine Interface and Communications, 1980, Jan., undated, 3 folders (Box 102)
  - GPU Man-Machine Communications Ad hoc Committee: Appendix A, 1979, July 5 (Box 102)
  - References for Final Draft of GPU Man-machine Communications Ad Hoc Committee, 1979, July 5 (Box 102)
  - Loose Natural Gas (LGTN information, undated) (Box 103)
  - A.G.A. Solar Energy Committee materials, 1978, Aug. 21 (Box 103)
  - American Gas Association: Report to Members, 1986-1988, 3 folders (Box 103)
  - Argonne National Laboratory:
    - 1984-1985 (Box 103)
    - Logos, Vo. 4, No. 1 and Vol. 7, No. 2 (Box 103)
  - Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory Annual Report, 1984 (Box 103)
  - Some Political Issues Related to Future Special Nuclear Materials Production, 1981, Aug. (Box 103)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory: Annual Report, 1984 (Box 103)
  - University of California Los Alamos National Laboratory: Research Highlights, 1986-1989, 4 folders (Box 103)
  - Response to questions posed to William McCollam, Jr. (Box 103)
  - Energy Supplied to Densely Populated Areas Exemplified by Manhattan Island, 1976, Sept. 21 (Box 103)
  - Science, Risk, and Public Policy, 1983, June 22 (Box 103)
  - Report for the Congressional Research Service: Library of Congress, 1978, Mar. (Box 103)
  - FPC Reports: Plant by Plant Deliveries of Fossil Fuels to Utilities, 1977, Apr. 25 (Box 103)
  - Remarks of the President at Signing Ceremony for H. R. 3809, Atomic Energy Act Amendments, 1983, Jan. 7 (Box 103)
  - Proposed Amendments to OMB, GSA, DOD, and NASA Procurement Regulations, 1983, Jan.-Feb. (Box 103)
  - Statement of Richard E. Disbrow, President, American Electric Power Company on H. R. 555, 1983, Apr. 28 (Box 103)
  - Information on H. R. 44 and Hydroelectric Relicensing, undated (Box 103)
  - Energy and Commerce 2125 RHOB, 1981, Aug. 10 (Box 103)
  - Update for Price-Anderson Act, undated (Box 103)
  - Nuclear Power Oversight Committee's Position:
    - Nuclear Energy and the National Energy Strategy, 1990, Nov. (Box 103)
    - Standardization, 1991, Apr. (Box 103)
  - Report on Light-Water Reactors, undated (Box 103)
  - Report on Regulatory and Standardization Activities, undated (Box 103)
  - United States Energy Association A Call for Action, undated (Box 103)
  - A Policy Paper on AFR's and Reprocessing, undated (Box 103)
  - Nuclear Agenda for the First 100 Days, undated (Box 103)
  - Report of the OSTP Working Group on Basic Research in the Department of Energy, 1978, May 1 (Box 103)
  - Interim Report on the French Blackout of December 19, 1978-1979, Feb. 8 (Box 103)
  - Report on Petroleum & Petrochemical Industries, 1979, Jan. 7 (Box 103)
  - A Study of Simulation and Safety Margins in Light Water Reactors, 1979, Aug. 26 (Box 103)
  - Simulator Training of Nuclear Reactor Operators, 1979, Nov. (Box 103)
  - Nuclear Cost Trends, 1980-1984 (Box 103)
  - Electric Power Transmission and Land Use Policy Papers, 1980, Apr. 7 (Box 103)
  - An Evaluation of the Selective Absorption Process for Removal of Krypton from the Containment Atmosphere at Three Mile Island Unit 2, 1980, May 22 (Box 103)
  - Shift Rotation Systems: Is one Less Physiologically and Psychologically Harmful Than Another, 1980, Nov. (Box 103)
  - Materials on U.S. Nuclear Power Licensing Process, 1981 (Box 103)
  - Summary of Industry Degraded Core Rulemaking Program, 1981, Mar. 31 (Box 103)
  - UNPOC Recommendation on Institutional Funding Arrangements for the Committee on Energy Awareness, 1981, June 10 (Box 103)
  - Nuclear Energy Policy: Recommendation of Emerging Issues Subcommittee, 1981, Sept. 9 (Box 103)
  - Various Statements and Remarks Concerning the Nuclear Energy Utility, 1981-1984 (Box 103)